http://www.dumptruckinsurance.com/about-us/privacy-policy/

Internet Privacy Policy - DumpTruckInsurance.com
At DumpTruckInsurance.com, we respect the privacy of our web site visitors.
Our Commitment
We do not gather any personal information about you unless you provide it to us knowingly.
We also recognize that this information belongs to you and that we must treat it accordingly.
We do gather typical anonymous, non-personal, information to help us improve our website.
Our Use of Personal and Non-Personal Information
We collect two kinds of information about our online visitors, personal and non-personal information.
Visitors are not required to register to access the public pages of DumpTruckInsurance.com.
Non-personal information.
As you use the Internet, a trail of anonymous information is left at each website you visit and is typically retained by the web server hosting each site.
We use this information to track the total number of visitors to DumpTruckInsurance.com and to guide our efforts to improve our site.
The non-personal information we monitor includes the browser type and operating system being used by our visitors; areas of the site visited;
date and time of access; host or service-provider information, and identification of the referring site.
This information is used exclusively for our internal purposes and is not disclosed to any non-affiliated third parties except our web site developers.
Personal information provided by you is kept confidential and is collected only when voluntarily offered by visitors
and is used solely for purposes that are clearly identified on our site.
Personal information may include name, title, company, address, phone number and similar information which identifies you.
We collect this information so that you may obtain access to members-only portions of our site and/or to receive products and services.
We do not sell or rent or transmit personal information to third party organizations,
except with those organizations that provide services on behalf of the site in the normal course of business, such as credit card processors.
These third parties may only use the data for the purpose for which it was provided.
DumpTruckInsurance.com does not seek personal information from children.
Our Use Of Cookies
DumpTruckInsurance.com may place an electronic "cookie" in the browser files of your computer to facilitate and enhance your communication and interaction with our site.
Many web sites use cookies for these purposes.
Cookies themselves do not enable us to access any personal information about our visitors; however, they do allow DumpTruckInsurance.com to analyze visitors' use of our site.
This analysis helps us better understand which areas of our sites are most useful and popular so we can plan improvements and updates accordingly.
DumpTruckInsurance.com does not use cookies to retrieve information from a visitor's computer that was not originally sent in a cookie.
Third Party Advertisers
We may use third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit this website.
These companies may use information (NOT including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits
to this and other websites, obtained via a standard cookie on your computer, in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
Internet Security
The security of your personal information is very important to us.
We attempt to provide for the secure transmission of your personal information from your computer to our servers by utilizing encryption software.
We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect.
Only those employees who need access to your information in order to perform their duties are allowed access to your personal information.
However, due to the inherent open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and DumpTruckInsurance.com, and DumpTruckInsurance.com and you,
will be free from unauthorized access by third parties such as hackers and your use of this site demonstrates your assumption of this risk.
DumpTruckInsurance.com does not assume any responsibility for any harm, loss, or damage you may experience or incur by the sending of personal or confidential information over the Internet by or to DumpTruckInsurance.com.
Consent
By using this site, you signify your consent to the DumpTruckInsurance.com  Internet Privacy Policy.
If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this web site.
We reserve the right, at our discretion, to update, change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy from time to time.
Any changes to this privacy policy will be promptly disclosed in this area.
This policy applies to DumpTruckInsurance.com and its affiliates.
